Raphael Jans Caballegan: present po
Chi o motomeru: am present sir
Raphael Jans Caballegan: yes po we can see
Chi o motomeru: hi 'morning!
Chi o motomeru: yez po sir
Raphael Jans Caballegan: hahahah
Chi o motomeru: mic test?
Chi o motomeru: HAHAHA
Raphael Jans Caballegan: mic test can you hear sir?
Raphael Jans Caballegan: yup i agree
Chi o motomeru: Oki na po
Mr. Sean: yes po
Mr. Sean: i agree sir
Mr. Sean: sir mic test
Mr. Sean: HAHAHAHAHA so funny
Raphael Jans Caballegan: anything in the world can be explained with science
Raphael Jans Caballegan: politics is a pretty hard topic to discuss
Raphael Jans Caballegan: how do i know if i am possessed by the holy spirit?